today is July 4th the day America broke
up with Great Britain and like most
recent singles we celebrate by eating as
many hot dogs as possible fill that void
Joey being single is great but more than
that it is your right so in honor of
Independence Day I present to you the
single person's Bill of Rights number
one you have the right to go home for
Christmas by yourself it's okay that
there's no one special in your life and
if Aunt Karen has a problem with that
she can go back to scrapbooking and
pretending to be happy her husband's
cancer is in
remission number two you have the right
to not be set up by your friends for the
last time no one wants to date your dog
walker sure he's got great calves but
he's also got a handful of soft Beagle
poop number three you have the right to
get a table for one yes Golden Corral
Hostess who asks just you I actually
prefer to eat alone because there's no
one to judge me when I make a fourth
trip to the dessert
bar and four you have the right to die
alone in a hospital bed where the nurses
don't even know your name with no one to
leave your belongings to your house
eventually slowly taken over by feral
cats and Drifters who enjoy your
possessions with no knowledge of your
existence on second thought maybe you
should try dating that dog walker I mean
he walks rescue dogs maybe he'll be down
to bang a rescue
person speaking of great calvs we've got
Jim Jeff on this week's not safe talking
about female orgasms oh there'll be
fireworks all right happy fourth
pervs hey this is Nikki Glazer and this
is the part of the video where I tell
you to watch more of my videos but I'm
not going to tell you what to do instead
I'm just going to look at you
judgingly